Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
- Series XIX. Health Studies
  - Occupational Injury and Illness among Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers (New York State and Pennsylvania), 1997-1999 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Environmental Health Priorities - New York State Department of Health, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Field Sanitation Study - Food Science - Cornell Migrant Program, 2000-04 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Environmental Health Risks in Rural Communities - Program Work Team, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Geographic Distribution of Migrant and Seasonal Harvest Workers in New York State, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Series XX. Farm Labor Studies and Reports, New York State
  - Viable Farmer-Worker Relationships (Adams, How, Larson), 1967 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Various Farm Labor Publications, 1976-1982 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Earnings of Migratory Farmworkers in Wayne Co. (New York State) 1968, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - ILR Study of New York State Farm Labor Policy (proposed by Ron Donovan), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Impact of Extending Unemployment Insurance to Agricultural Workers, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Consideration in Extending Unemployment Insurance to Agricultural Workers in New York State - Ward Bauder, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Interdepartmental Committee on Migrant Labor - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Labor Management Practices on Selected NY Dairy Farms, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Apple Harvest Labor Productivity in the Champlain Valley (New York State), 1977 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Labor Productivity of Apple Harvest Workers (Dennis U. Fisher), 1978 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Labor Management Study on Selected Monroe County (New York State) Farms, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Farm Labor Regulations (New York State) - Dennis U. Fisher, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Model Legislation Re: Farmworkers (New York State) - Stuart J. Mitchell, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Study of State-Federal Employment Standards for Seasonal Farm Work (New York State Dept. of Labor), 1979 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Farmworker Rights Booklets, 1979, 1985, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Management of Migrant Labor in the Pennsylvania Apple Harvest - Holt/Burton, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Agricultural Labor Management, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Employment Demand Study - Arthur Berkey, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Farm Labor Management - Home Study Course (Ag. Econ., Cornell), 1982 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Managing Seasonal Hired Labor - C. Arthur Bratton and R. Brian How, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Labor Management Practices on New York Dairy Farms - Bratton/Kwiatkowski, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Farmworker Minimum Wage Order (New York State), 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - New York Job Service Program Year 1986 MSFW Outreach Plan, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Farm Labor Regulations - Dale Grossman and Mark Henderson, 1986, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Human Resource Management on the Farm...Letter Series (New York State), 1988 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Laws Protecting the Farmworker in New York State (New York State Dept. of Labor), 1988 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Wages and Benefits of Full Time Non Family Employees on Larger that Average New York State Dairy Farms - Maloney and Woodruff, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Farm Labor Management Program - Cornell/Ag. and Markets, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Gov. Mario Cuomo's Task Force on Agricultural Employment, Education and Labor (1), 1989 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Gov. Mario Cuomo's Task Force on Agricultural Employment, Education and Labor (2), 1989 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Gov. Mario Cuomo's Task Force on Agricultural Employment, Education and Labor (3), 1989 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Final Report Task Force on Agricultural Employment, Education and Labor, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Follow-Up Cornell Study on Collective Bargaining and Other Public Policy, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Collective Bargaining Task Force (ILR, Human Ecology, CALS), 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Understanding the New York State Farm Minimum Wage Law (New York State Dept. of Labor), 1989 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Changes in the New York State Farm Minimum Wage Law - Maloney/Embrey, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Dairy Farm Worker Training at Tompkins Cortland Community College - Maloney/Jule, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - The Farm Labor Contractor System in New York State (New York State Dept. of Labor), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Farmworker's Guide to New York State Labor Laws (New York State Dept. of Labor), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - New York State Agricultural Workforce Certification Pilot Program, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Summary of State and Federal Regulations - Guide for Farmers, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Separate and Unequal - New York's Farmworkers - Senate-Assembly, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Labor Cost and Food - Engman Estimate, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Dairy Worker Issues - Kay Embrey and Farmworkers, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Farmworker Legal Services of New York - Five Year Priority Process, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Training Needs Assessment of Farm Workers New York State, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Protection for Farm Workers (New York State Dept. of Labor), 2002 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Farm Labor Regulations - Dale Arrison Grossman and Jason D. Minard, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Managing Hispanic Workers - Richard Stup and Thomas Maloney, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 49)
- Series XXI. Farmworker Studies and Reports
  - Subseries XXIa. New York State
    - Bibliographies - Migrant Farmworkers, 1966-2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Latinos in the U.S. - Selected Sources - New York State Library, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Directories Related to Farmworkers (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Farmworker Journal (Farmworker Data Network), 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Kay's Clips (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Noticias y notas (New York State) Examples, 2001-06 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Farmworker Justice News (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - New York's Harvest Labor, 1943-1948 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Farm and Food Processing Labor 1959 Annual Report - New York State, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Extension Home Economics and "Migrant" Labor (New York State), 1960-1969 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Migrant Farm Workers in Western New York: Changes - Young and John, 1951-1978 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Making Sociology Relevant (Includes Research on Migrant Farmworkers) - William H. Friedland, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Migrant Labor in Upstate New York - Jeffrey Hoffman and Richard Seltzer, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Earnings of Migratory Farmworkers in Wayne County, New York, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Labor Waste in New York State: Rural Exploitation and Migrant Workers (Friedland), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Who Are the Rural Poor? - Lyle Raymond, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - The Migrant: A Human Perspective (New York State), 1972 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Agricultural Mechanization and the Migrant in New York State - Howard W. Taylor, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - The Dynamics of Migratory Settlement in Wayne County, New York State, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Minority Workers on New York State Farms - W.W. Bauder, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Economic Independence...A Meaningful Opportunity for Farmworkers - Karen Tobin, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - The Process of Mutual Impacts...Educational Program to Migrant Children - Stephen Johnson, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Agricultural Technology and the Migrant Farmworker - G. Levine, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Social Services for Migrant and Seasonal Farm Laborers (New York State), 1976 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Plight of Rural Women in Upstate New York - Hortence Cochrane, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Definitions of Seasonal Farmworker - Suffolk Co. (New York) Migrant Affairs Council, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Report on the Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers - Mario C. Cuomo, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Farmworker Women's Equity Project - Rural New York Opportunities, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Migrant Farmworkers in Western New York, 1978 - Young, John, Hermann, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Migrant Report - Elizabeth Reilinger and Candance Widmer, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Geneseo Migrant Center (in "Synergist") - Gloria Mattera, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Program Needs of Migrant Farmworkers in Wayne County - Kay Embrey, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Farmwork and Farmworkers in New York State (in "Prepare") - Stuart Mitchell, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Survey of Farm Labor Related Needs of Cooperative Extension Agents, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - My Piece of the Rock (Willie's Valley) (New York) - Elizabeth Mascle, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Migrants in Western Ne York: Their Needs and Agencies Attempting to Meet Those Needs - David Parmalee, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Haitian Migrant Workers in Wayne County, New York - Yuriko Yamashita, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Orchard and Vineyard Survey (New York), 1985 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - New York Agriculture 2000 - Donald Butcher, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Employment and Economic Profiles of Migrant Farmworkers - Chi, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Farm Families - Fact Sheets 1-5, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Background for Liberalism to the Test: African-American Farmworkers, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Liberalism to the Test: African-American Migrant Farmworkers and the State of New York - Don Barr, et. al., 1988 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Agricultural Studies in the Geneseo/Finer Lakes Region (New York State), 1988 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - A Tale of Two Homes (Migrant Labor Housing) - Peter S.K. Chi, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - The Presence and Absence of Farmworker Families in the Migrant Stream - Roberts (pages 1-151), 1990 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - The Presence and Absence of Farmworker Families in the Migrant Stream - Roberts (pages 152-end), 1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Migrants - The Invisible Workers -(Nick DeLuca), 1991 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - New York Dairy Industry, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Research on Migrant Farmworkers in New York State - Chi, White-Means, McClain, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Children of Migrant Farmworkers (in Rural Affairs), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - New York State Labor Laws...Farm or Food Processing Employment - New York Dept. of Labor, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Women in the Migrant Agricultural Labor Force - Kay Embrey, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Student Voice: Migrant Students' Writing Experiences - Nancy Zimmet, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Changing Landscape of New York Agriculture - B.F. Stanton, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Race and Ethnic Change in New York State - Hirschl and Tran, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Opening Closed Doors: Perceptions of African American Parents and White Teachers - Kathy Castania Fox Dissertation, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - NY Intrastate Migrant Families' Access to Human Services, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Migrant Farm Work in New York State - Josiah Levitan-Reine, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - 1993 Farm Program (Inspections) - New York State Dept. of Labor, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Mexican Migrant Farmworkers (Wayne County, New York State) - Raul Zelaya, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Survey of Migrant Agricultural Workers in Wayne County, New York, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Agricultural Dispute Resolution (Industrial and Labor Relations), 1994-1996 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Adverse Minimum Wage (H2-A) - Cornell Study, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Farmworker Issues on Dairy Farms (New York State) - Kay Embrey, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Women Latino Migrant Farmworkers (New York State) - Patricia L. Biermayr-Jenzano, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Migrant Farmworkers Records in Upstate New York, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Management of Hispanic Employees on New York Dairy Farms - Thomas R. Maloney, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - The Voice of Farmworkers - Justice for Farmworkers - New York State, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Mediator Case Session - Farmworker Issues, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - 2000 Agriculture and Food Systems In-Service, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Who Will Farm? Farming Alternatives Program, Cornell, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Latino/Hispanic History and Culture in New York State - New York State Archives, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Low Income Student Transiency (New York State) - Kai Schafft, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Hudson Valley Farmworker Report (New York State) - Bard College Migrant Labor Project, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Immigrants and the Community - Max J. Pfeffer and Pilar Parra, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - La Trabajadora Agricola y Sus Derechos (FLSNY), 2004 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Subseries XXIb. Regional
    - Migratory Farm Workers in the Atlantic Coast Stream (Western New York State), 1953 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Migratory Farm Workers in the Atlantic Coast Stream - Larson/Sharp, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - The Poor Don't Want to Be Middle-Class - Robert Coles, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - The Lives of Migrant Farmers - Robert Coles, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Sociological Patterns Among Michigan Migrant Workers, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - The California Migrant Farmworker, His Family and the Rural Community, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Migratory Agricultural Workers in the Eastern Seaboard States - Larson, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - A Response to Marginality - The Case of Migrant Farmworkers -- Dorothy Nelkin, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Life Styles of Migrants on the Season and their Adaptations to Community Attitudes - Ira E. Harrison, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Working with Migrants - Robert Coles and Tom Davey (New Republic), 1970 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Child Labor, 1971-1990 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Invisible Migrant Workers - Dorothy Nelkin (in "Society"), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Migration and Modernization - Ghulam Mohammed Samdani, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Fresh Air Sweatshop: Child Labor on the Farm (New Generation), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Social and Economic Characteristics of Spanish-Origin Farmworkers (USDA), 1973 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - The Teamsters' Campaign to Smash a Union (in "Readers Digest"), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Keeping the Migrant Stream Flowing (in "Manpower") - Algeria, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Some Differential Aspects of Participation in Migrant and Seasonal Farm Worker Human Services Program Decision-Making - Ernest F. Powers, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - The Migrant - A Saga Without a Villain - League of Women Voters, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Agricultural Unionism and the Early New Deal - Cletus E. Daniel, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - USDA Reports on the Migrant Farm Worker, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - The Migrant Farmworker - U.S. Catholic Conference, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - An Analysis of Selected Dept. of Labor Projects for Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Migrant Child Welfare (InterAmerica Research Associates), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Migrant Child Welfare - A Review of the Literature and Legislation, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Migrant Child Welfare - Executive Summary, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Agricultural Labor Project of Coca-Cola, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Labor's Dwindling Harvest - Impact of Mechanization... (CA), 1978 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Groundswell - Edited by Kathy Cecil and Kathleen Connell, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Foreign Workers - A Question of Property Rights (Dennis U. Fisher), 1979 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Economic Incentives Facing Mexican Migrant Workers (Oregon), 1979 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Agricultural Labor in 1980 (University of Texas), 1980 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - The Farmworker in the U.S. - Farmworker Data Network, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Perspectives on the Structure of American Agriculture (USDA), 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - The Education of Nonmetro Hispanics (USDA), 1981 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Poverty in America - Definitions and Trends Over the Past Two Decades, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - A Case Study of the Evolution of Mexican Migration to the U.S., 1981 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - The Eastern Migrant Stream - Disciples of Christ, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Migration, Population Growth and Development 1950-2000, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Breaking the Cycle of Poverty Among Farmworkers, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Unscrambling the Hired Farmworker Stereotype (in "Farmline," USDA), 1983 (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Farm Labor Unions (From "The Nation"), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - The Changing Migrant Scene - A Conference, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Migrant Working in the U.S.: A Brief Report - Sharon Colson, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Agricultural Statistics, 1984-1998 (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Immigration: What we Promised, Where to Draw the Line, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Characteristics of Agricultural Work Force Households (USDA), 1987 (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - The Last Plantation (USDA) in "Common Course Magazine", 1987 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - The H2-A Program - Protections for U.S. Farmworkers (GAO), 1988 (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Illegal Aliens - Influence...on Wages and Working Conditions (GAO), 1988 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - More that One Journey - Charles Jackson, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - The Effects of Migration on Children - An Ethnographic Study, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    - Food Cost Review (USDA), 1989 (Box 46, Folder 53)
    - Working Group on Farm Labor and Rural Poverty (California), 1989 (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - Subseries XXIc. U.S.
    - After the Harvest: The Plight of Older Farmworkers - AARP, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Unauthorized Migration: An Economic Development Response, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Farmworkers Face Gaps in Protection and Barriers to Benefits (GAO), 1991 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Farm Employment and Wage Rates 1910-1990 (USDA), 1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Report of the Commission on Agricultural Workers, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Report of the Commission on Agricultural Workers - Executive Summary, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Commission on Agricultural Workers - Case Studies and Research Reports, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Agricultural Workers - Hearings and Workshops, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - A Geographic Analysis of Seasonal Agricultural Services Farms (USDA), 1992 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Mixtec Migrant Farmworkers in California Agriculture, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Services for Migrant Children - The Urban Institute, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - An Example of the Effects of Immigration Reform ... - Enrique Figueroa, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Migrant Farmworkers in the U.S. (Implementation of Helsinki Accords), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Pre-Harvest Conference (U.S. Dept. of Labor), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Hired Farm Labor Use on Fruit, Vegetable and Horticultural Specialty Farms - USDA, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Farmworkers in the Post-IRCA Period (NAWS No. 4, U.S. Dept. of Labor), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Migrant Farmworkers: Pursuing Security in an Unstable Labor Market, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Migrant Farmworkers and their Children (ERIC), 1994 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - National Legal Conference on Immigration and Refugee Policy, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Association of Farmworkers Opportunity Programs Biennial Report, 1994-1996 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Immigration and Ethnic Communities: A Focus on Latinos - Refugio I. Rochin, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Racial/Ethnic Minorities in Rural Areas - 1980-1990, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Immigration and the Changing Face of Rural America - Philip Martin, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - The U.S. Food Industry - Geoffrey M. Green, Edward W. McLaughlin, Kristin Park, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Focus on People - Fresh Produce Industry - Edward W. McLaughlin, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Treaty of Guadalupe Hidalgo - Refugio I. Rochin, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Fields Without Borders - Student Activism With Farmworkers, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Employee Compensation and Job Satisfaction on Dairy Farms (N.E. U.S.), 1999 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Balancing Acts: Toward a Fair Bargain on Seasonal Agricultural Workers, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - National Farmworker Fact Sheet - Student Action for Farmworkers, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Farmworkers in Canada, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Amber Waves of Gain - American Farm Bureau, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Farmworker Awareness Conference - Catholic Charities, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - What Federal Statistics Reveal about Migrant Farmworkers (ERIC), 2002 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - The Migrant/Seasonal Phenomena in Agriculture (USDA), 2004 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Major Concepts and Issues in the Field of Collective Bargaining (MI), 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Guide to Child Labor Provisions of the Fair Labor Standards Act (U.S. Dept. of Labor), 1971 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - California Hired Farm Labor and Law, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Marketing Orders and the Structure of Agriculture - A.V. Krebs, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Farmworker Job Training: A National Response to a National Blemish, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Farm Labor Contracting in the U.S., 1981 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Federal and State Employment Standards and U.S. Farm Labor, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Labor Expenditures...Immigration Reform (USDA), 1989 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Coordination of Migrant and Season Farmworker Season Programs - Martin, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Farm Workers in the U.S. (Florida Sugar Cane Workers), 1992 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Alien Farmworkers in American Agriculture - University of California, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Immigration Reform and American Agriculture (USDA), 1984 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - From Labor Contracting in the U.S., 1981 - USDA, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - The H2-A Program - Protections for U.S. Farmworkers (GAO), 1988 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Farmworker Protective Laws - A Guide for Farmworkers, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Summary of Federal Laws and Regulations Affecting Agricultural Employers, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Impact of Immigration Act of 1986 on Farm Labor Contracting - Figueroa, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Will Immigration Reform Affect the Economic Competitiveness of Labor-Intensive Crops? - U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Commission on Agricultural Workers (U.S.), 1991 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Agricultural Workers' Rights - Ag. Labor Relations Board, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - How to Stabilize Your Farm Work Force (University of CA), 1995 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - H-2A Agricultural Guestworker Program (General Accounting Office), 1997 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - H-2A Agricultural Guestworker Program (General Accounting Office), 1998 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Workforce Management for Farms... - NRAES, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - A Handbook on the California Agricultural Relations Law, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Alternatives to Immigrant Labor? - Center for Immigration Studies, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Series XXII. Farmworker Related Organizations
  - Farm Worker Women's Institute (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Geneseo Migrant Center - Gloria Mattera, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Farm workers Association - H. Engman, 1975-1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Interagency Coordinating Committee on Migrant and Rural Poor, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Rochester (New York) Farm worker Rights Organization, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)